{
  "id": "flashcard-english-5-unit-6",
  "title": "Tiếng Anh Lớp 5 - Unit 6",
  "subject": "english",
  "tags": [
    "english-5",
    "unit6",
    "vocab"
  ],
  "description": "Từ vựng Unit 6: Our schoolrooms",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "around",
      "answer": "xung quanh",
      "speak": "around"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "library",
      "answer": "thư viện",
      "speak": "library"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "ground/first/second/… floor",
      "answer": "tầng trệt/tầng 1/tầng 2/...",
      "speak": "ground/first/second/… floor"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "art",
      "answer": "nghệ thuật",
      "speak": "art"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "music",
      "answer": "âm nhạc",
      "speak": "music"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "computer",
      "answer": "máy tính",
      "speak": "computer"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "way",
      "answer": "con đường, cách",
      "speak": "way"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "upstairs",
      "answer": "trên lầu",
      "speak": "upstairs"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "downstairs",
      "answer": "dưới lầu",
      "speak": "downstairs"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "along",
      "answer": "dọc theo",
      "speak": "along"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "past",
      "answer": "ngang qua",
      "speak": "past"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "corridor",
      "answer": "hành lang",
      "speak": "corridor"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "turn",
      "answer": "rẽ, quay",
      "speak": "turn"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "break time",
      "answer": "giờ giải lao",
      "speak": "break time"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "left",
      "answer": "bên trái",
      "speak": "left"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "right",
      "answer": "bên phải",
      "speak": "right"
    }
  ]
}